Guide to the El Corno Emplumado Archive 1959-1969 MSS.011
Fales Library and Special Collections
El Corno Emplumado Archive
1959-1969
Fales Library and Special Collections
Randall, Margaret, 1936-
MSS.011
5.25 Linear Feet in 9 manuscript boxes and 3 half manuscript boxes.
El Corno Emplumado was a literary magazine of poetry, prose, letters and art from two hemispheres, printed in Spanish and English. Margaret Randall founded the magazine in 1962 in an attempt to unite the literatures of the Americas. Published from Mexico, Margaret Randall and Sergio Mondragon co-edited the magazine until 1969 when Robert Cohen joined Randall as co-editor for the final two issues.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Historical Note
Margaret Randall began El Corno Emplumado in 1962 and co-edited the little magazine at various times with Sergio Mondragon and Robert Cohen. The magazine was highly regarded as a progressive literary journal by poets and intellectuals throughout the Americas. Each issue includes original writings in Spanish and in English as well as translations. El Corno Emplumado was deeply committed to a revolutionary literature and developed an independent press that published works such as a mini-anthology of Cuban revolutionary poetry. As the magazine progressed, Margaret Randall became increasingly radical in her politics. Randall's vision of the little magazine as a forum dedicated to revolutionary literature addressing progressive intellectuals and revolutionaries themselves caused a rift between her and her co-editor Sergio Mondragon. As a result, Robert Cohen replaced Mondragon as co-editor for the final two issues in 1969.
Scope and Content Note
El Corno Emplumado attempted to connect the literatures of North, Central, and South America and in doing so, to create a sense of solidarity between hemispheres. The collection contains Margaret Randall's personal notebooks, poetry, writings, and correspondence as well as correspondence between editors and contributors, typescripts, and galley proofs for El Corno Emplumado.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in three series. Series A: Margaret Randall includes Margaret Randall's biography, personal correspondence, notebooks, poems, and other wirtings. Series B: El Corno Emplumado Correspondence contains correspondence between the editors of the magazine and the contributors. Series C: Printed Materials includes an incomplete collection of printed materials divided into three subseries. Subseries 1 includes annotated typescripts for issues 24-31. Subseries 2 consists of page proofs for issues 24-30. Subseries 3 contains galley proofs for issues 24, 25, 27-31.
Series A and Series C are organized chronologically. The Correspondence in Series B is organized alphabetically by the writer's last name.
Missing Title
Series A: Margaret Randall
Series B: En Corno Emplumado Correspondence
Series B: El Corno Emplumado Correspondence
Series C: Printed Materials
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials but that have been physically separated or removed.
Mexico City (Mexico); New York (N.Y.).; Havana (Cuba); Spanish American poetry |y 20th century.; Revolutionary poetry, Spanish American |x Translations into English.; Revolutionary poetry, Cuban.; Randall, Margaret, |d 1936-; Correspondence.; Diaries; Galley proofs.; Typescripts; Ginsberg, Allen, 1926-1997; Gitlin, Todd; Guevara, Celia; Mondragón, Sergio; Blu, Robert; Wakoski, Diane; Randall, Margaret, 1936-
- Series A: Margaret Randall
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains Margaret Randall's biography, personal correspondence, notebooks, poems, and other writings.
  - Biographical information, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence. Margaret Randall to Sergio Mondragon. [originals located in box 8, legal folder], undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Notebook, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Notebook, June-November 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Poems, June-December 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Poems, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Poems, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Poems 1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Poems, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Poems, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Breakfast and the Whole Glass, Poems: 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Poems, 1965; Other Writings, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Poems, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Poems and Other Writings, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Poems, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Undated poems, Editor's notes (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Writings: Javier Heraud and Rosa Hurtarte, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Writings: Gonzalo Rojas and Lucien Sebag, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Writings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Series B El Corno Emplumado Correspondence
  - Angel, Jerome B. Aldan, Daisy, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Claribel Alegria, Fernando, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Alexander, D. Alexander, Floyce, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Alimard, Amin Abgel, Fernandez Miguel, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Angel Margarinos Velilla, Juan Antillano, Laura, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Antin, David Aponte, Rene Rivera, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Araba, M.R.E. Arabgim Carlos Alberto, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Aray, Edmundo Arenal de Rodriguez, Electa Argente, Hector, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Arguello-Sansir, Eduardo y Kathy Ardijis, Honero Arnoni, Menahem S., undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Arrabal, Fernando Asano, Takeji Athas, Nini, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "A" Miscellaneous Acosta, Mary Jane Acosta, Oscar Acosta, Sofia Adler, Judy Agent, Dan De Alas, Alejandro Alfonso-Sanchez, Jose Maria Alva, Arturo Castillo Alwan, Ameen Anderson, Byron Andrews, Lyman Angel, Arturo Dubra Arvanitis, Sonia Arturo, Francisco Astudillo, Jorge Romaini Agusto, A. Ayon, Wai Ayala Echavarri, Rafael Ana Maria, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ballestros, Rafael Bandt, Miguel Banks, Russel, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Barefoot, Dabjinsky Barrientos, Jaime Barrios, Alvero, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Bartra, Agusti Bastian, Heiner Batllo, Jose, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bayes, Ronald Beard, Bill Beckett, Samuel, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Belpair Berge, Carol, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Berke, D. Joseph Bertica, Carlos Minerva Bertica, Carita Miriam, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Betancourt, Alberto Bianchedi, Remo Bianchi, Ciro, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Billingsley, Allie Ward Bishop, Gordon Blackburn, Paul, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Blackburn, Sara Bly, Robert Bock, Layeh and Philip, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bookstores, Radio, Television, Cinema, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Boss, Bob Botsford, Keith, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bowring, Angela Bowring, George, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Boyd, Blair Branch, Donna Brandi, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Braverman, Connie Bringham, Besmilr, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brilliant, Alan [Unicorn Press], undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Brower, G. and K. Brown, Bill Brown, Geoffrey, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Brown, Michael Brown, Paul Bruce, Lennart, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Brushwood, John Brutus, Denis Buckmaster, Charles, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Buffington, Mel and Beverly Buhle, Paul Burns, Bruce and Ellen, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "B" Miscellaneous Babarsky, Mrs. Edrica Bavez, Mecka Baldwin, Michael Masak, Subimal Batista, Moreno Rene Beissel, Henry Bell, Dorothy Beltran, Luis Benford, Lawrence Bengolea, Rosa Benjamin, Jeramiah Benn, Robert Michael Bermeja, Enrique Bigger, duss Blassingame, Roy Blackburn, Frank Bond, Richard Bondy, Sebastian Brady, Elena Brand, Miller Brewer, Kenneth Briggs, Harold Bravo-Espinosa, Freddy Brossard, Nicole Bruns, Richard Burke, Nerbert Busch, Alfredo Omar Burten, F. Butcher, Grace, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Cabral, Olga Calderon, Arturo Cardenal, Ernesto, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Carrero, Jaime Carroll, Paul Casa de las Americas, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Carlin De G., Marcelo Chavez, Alfardo L. Choudhury, Paradip and Malay Roy, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Ciardi, John Clark, Michele Clays, Gino, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Clayton, Harold Coahley, William Cobas, Socrates, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Codrescu, Andrei Coffeen, Carlos Cohen, George, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Cohen, Robert David Colchie, Tom Coleman, Victor, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Collom, Jack Comfort, Thomas E. Corman, Cid, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Cramb, Beverly S. Creeley, Robert Cuadra, Pablo Antonio, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Cunard, Nancy Cunliffe, David ad Tina Morris, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - "C" Miscellaneous Calderon, Ricardo A. Calvillo, Manuel Campbell Campos, Haraldo de Candelaira, Frederick Cantillano, Juan A. Dardenas, Daniel Cargas, Harry Carmona, Lucia Carpy, Enrique Garcia Carr, John Carrington, Gabriel Caxton, Leonora Castano, Pedro Castrilloalva, Arturo Chandler, Wehlan Chandra Saha, Subhas Coffin, Raymond Cohen, Fredrick F. Cohen, William H. Collins, Mrs. Arthur Contijoch, Josefa Cooney, Seamus Cooperman, Stanley Corey, Ruth Cortes, Enrique Cotensin, Patrice Coulson, Bruce Covrey, Pierre Coxhead, David Crews, Mrs. J.C. Culla, Daniel, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Dahl, Ronald Dakin, Karen Dalton, Roque, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dane, Barbara David, Bianne Davidson, DeWitt A., undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Davidson, Ned Davis, William DeLoach, Allen, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - de Kooning, Elaine de Kooning, William, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - De Puy, Rini Templeton Desleal, Alvaro Menen Dessauer, Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Diaz Martinez, Manuel Diaz, Tania, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Di Palma, Raymond Di Prima, Diane Dobel, Ken, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dobkin, David Dorn, Edward Dowden, George, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "D" Micellaneous Davies, Roger Duraeme, Denis Disiz, Carlos F. Domiguez, Emilio Doria, C Dowling, John Drach, Natalie Dudley, Allen Duque Naranjo, Lisandro Dusenberg, Gail Dyer, Alan, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Earlich, Reese Economu, George and Rochelle Edwards, Alicia, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Eigner, Larry Emiolio, Jose Erhard, Thomas, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Eshleman, Clayton, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Estrado, Angel, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - "E" Miscellaneous Espinoza, Carlos Etter, Dave Evans, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Faunell, Dean Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Ferro, Martha Field, Edward Fierro, Danubie Terres, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Fitch, Andrew forest, Bernard Forester, Merlin, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Fox, Connie Fraire, Isabel Frank, Howard, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Franklyn, Frederic Frappier, Jon Fremantle, Anne, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Frieder, Jackqueline Fromadier, Noel, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - "F" Miscellaneous Fagan, William M. Fernandez, Carlos Fernandez, Oscar Fernandez, Ruth Finneran, Pat Fiofori, Tami Fonesca, Carlos Forbes, Christina Frese, Marcos R. Frye, Mary Fried, Edmund, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Gallegos, Epinosa Estuardo Gamez, Tana de Garcia-Pandavenes, Bernardo, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Gardner, Donald Gatten, Tom Gavronsky, Serge, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Geist, Sidney Georgakas, Dan, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Ginsberg, Louis Gitlin, Todd Goodell, Larry, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Grahm, Mary and Lawrence Grande, Felix Greenberg, Alvin, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Grieder, Theodore [regarding NYU collection], undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Grinberg, Miguel Gronowicz, Antoni Grosberg, Carol, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Guerrero, Hernando Guevera, Celia, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - "G" Miscellaneous Gabriella, Rolando Garcia-Barbon, Manuel Garces Larrea, Cristobal Garcia, Carlos Garzon, F. Garzotto, Leonard Golding, Mike Goldsmith, Carol Goldsmith, Janice Gonzalez, Eduardo Gonzalez-Martin, Jeronimo Pablo Grant, Mrs. A.R. Green, Charles J. Guzman, Rolando Andrade, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Hadassah Harris, Marguerite Harris, William, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Hartz, James Hedley, Leslie Woolf Heinze, Russell, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Henkin Jr. William A. Hennart, Michael Hierro, Patricia, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Hill, John Hirschman, Jack Hodley, Diana, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Holcomb, Michael Hopenhaym, Mabel Huizer, Gerrit, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - "H" Miscellaneous Hahn, Mrs. Esther Hatcher, Charles Hays, H.R. Henderson, David Hernandez, Agetro Armando Hernandez, Armas Joaquin Hernandez, David Holmberg, Mats Howell, Jon Huertas Jourda, Jose,lb/> Hoer, C, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Ignatow, David Ishmael, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Jamis, Fayad Jaramillo, Carlos Eduardo, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Johnson, Halvard Juarroz, Roberto, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Jore, Francisco Janson, Joseph, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Kapelner, Alan Katz, Leandro Katz, Vanessa, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Katz, Zulema Kearns, Lionel Kelder, Robert and Nini, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Keller, Walter Kelly, Robert Kern, Robert, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Kerr, Darrell Kissam, Edward Knowland, Nick, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Kohn, Gabriel Kowit, Steve Kretz, Tom, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "K" Miscellaneous Kahn, Matthew Karpilow, Miles Kelder-Hough, Sebastian Kenslo, Alyosha Kleinman, Margaret Knox, Hugh Kohn, Jaakov Kozer, Jose Krauss, Ruth, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Landollfe, Elvio La Rose, John Leslie, Alfred, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Levertov, Denise Levine, Naomi Levine, Stephen, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Lewis, Harry Lichtveld, Larion Linde, Jed, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Little Magazines A-G, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Little Magazines H-P, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Little Magazine R-Z, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lolo, Eduardo Long, Gerald Lowenfels, Lillian, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Lowenfels, Walter Luce Jr., Ralph A., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - "L" Miscellaneous Lawrence, David Leal, Menende Leiterman, Margaret Leo, R.S. Le Sueur, Meridel Lillard, Charles Limas Sousas, Miltende Lippincot, Proctor Lluch, Carmen Lopez, Roberto Castillo Luhn, David Ryan Luna, Alfredo Breilh Lynn, R., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - McCarthy, Michael B. McCord, Howard MacDonald, Nancy, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - MacKintosh, Don MacLow, Jackson McNamara, Tom, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Maguire, Micha Mailer, Norman Major, Clarence, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Marcus, Morton Martin, John Martin, Jose Luis, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Matter de Agrasemena, Olga Elena Matthews, Bill, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Matthews, Joan Mecham, James Mehrotra, Arvind, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Mendez, Jose Miguel Merton, Thomas, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Misscellaneous Correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Mondragon, Sergion de, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Montenegro, Guillermo Montgomery, George Moore, Marianne, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Moraff, Barbara Morales, Beltran Morejon, Nancy, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Morris, Richard Mottram, Eric Murray, Michele, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - "M" Miscellaneous MicGilvery, Lawrence McGrantle, Tom Magee, Wes Maldonado, Jesus Marty, Sid Matthewson, Bill Mathieu, Santiago Mauleon, Dr. Isodore Mavrakis, Nasso Medina, Richard Mednick, Murray Mehling, Joseph Mele, Frank Miller, Beth Kurti Milli, Oscar Morgan, Patrick Mund, Hugo, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Nandy, Pritish Nogueras, Luis Rogelio, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - "n" Miscellaneous Newman, Julia Newman, Paul Niederman, Fred Nordfors, Margaret Noyman, Louis, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Ochoa, Enriqueta Ocqueteaux, Leon Olsen, Betty Weiss, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Orlovsky, Peter Orrillo, Winston Ossman, David, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Osterlund, Steve Owens, Rochelle, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - "O" Miscellaneous Obregon, Robert Ochester, Edward Older, Julia Opalov, Leonard Orr, David ,lb/> Ortega-Heller, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Padero, Manuel Padin, Clemente Pagan, Evelyn A., undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Pages, Olivia Andres Gonzales Pasamanik, Luisa Peden, Petch, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Peden, William Pepita, Nana Peralta, Bertalicia, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Pereiro, Quintoio Manuel, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Perez Sarduy, Pedro Perret, Christopher Petersen, Valerie and Donald G., undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Peterson, Will Phelps, Donald Pickerill, William, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Pineda Bojorquez, Raul Pinedo Pajuelo, Jose Pizani, Leonardo, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Planz, Allen Polarias, Guillermo Ponzo, Albert Luis, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Price, Barret, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Publishers, Printers, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Purdy, Alfred W., undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - "P" Miscellaneous Pages, Itenri Paideussi, Elieni Paladini, Jorge Papini, Hilton Parr, Malcolm Pass, Marcelo Pena, Gerardo Perez, Celida y P. Perez, Floridor Perez, Francisco Perez Torres Llosa, Ricardo Piercy, Marge Pitol, Sergio Pole, Nelson and Susan Pool, Pat Pridgen, Charles Punnet, Ron, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Quarnali, Paola Querejeta, Alejandro Quin, Ann, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Rainer, Dachine Ramon, Angel Randall, Ellie, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Randall, John Randall, John P. Raworth, Tom, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Ray, Ginny Rechy, John Restrepo, Hector Amibal, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Reveuelta, Manuel Reynolds, Isabel Teynolds, Tim and Isabel, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Riccio, Ottone M. Robles, Victor Garcia Rocasolano, Albert, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Rodriguez, Miraim Rogelio, Luis Roman, Nazario, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Rosado, Julio Rosemont, Franklin Rosenberg, David, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Rossi, Matti Rothenberg, Jerome Rozeboom, Ariane and Arie, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Rudd, Mark, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - "R" Miscellaneous Robago, Joaquin Radin, Doris Reynolds, Amy Ricapito, J.V. Richardson, Val Rivera, Rene Rivero, Joel Rivero, Mario Robinson, Jeremy Rodley, Gerald Rock, E.S. Rodriguez, Ernesto Rodriguez, Rafael Romero, Armando Rowe, William Ruano, Manuel Ruiz de la Cuesta, Francisco Rumaker, Michael Ryan, Frederick, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Salado, Minerva Salkey, Andrew Sandberg, David, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Sanders, T. Salkey, Andrew Sandberg, David, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - S'chara, Julio Cesar Schwerner, Armand Sebba, George, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Segal, Antonio Seidman, High Sender, Luis E., undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Serpa, Robert Sherman, Susan, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Shoemaker, Jack Silliman, Ronald Silva, Ludovico, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Simon, John Oliver Sloman, Joel Sloman, Judy, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Sloman, Carl Sorrentino, Gilbert Souza, Raymond D., undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Stone, Edward Suardiaz, Luis Suarez, Maria del Carmen, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Sugarman, George, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Support letters re: El Corno Emplumado, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Sward, Robert, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - "S" Miscellaneous Saladana, Excilia Salek, Dennis Salvador, Raul Sainchef, Angel Salazar Garciz, Joaquin Sandoval, Joe Sanchez, Gustavo Santoro, Roberto Savory, Tzo Schielder, Diane Schoettler, Jim Schreiber, Ron Schoettler, Jim Schreiber, Ron Schutte, Rainer Sharma, Shri P.H. Shafer, Jose P. Shelby, Marian Sherwin, Judith Silva, Hector Silverman, Herschel Simmons, Merle E. Sharda, Jeffrey Smith, George Smedley Sondheim, Alan Sopend, Florinda Steingesser, Martin Stelrey, Carla Stisi, Irene Stout, Robert Joe Suarez, Carlos, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Taggart, John Tagliabue, John Tajiri, Shinkichi, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Tammer, David Tarn, Nathaniel Thiel, Paul, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Titus-Carmel, Gerard Tobias, Lilian Topor, Roland, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Torriente, Madeline Vivo de la Tovar, Juan Trachtenberg, Alan, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Trachtenberg, George Truesdale, C. William, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Uhtoff, Marv Urondo, Francisco, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Viljalo, David Valle, Ernesto R del Valle, Fransisco, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Van Newkirk, Allen Vas Dias, Robert Veeder, Rex, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Vega, Nicholas Reina Verma, Vinay K. Vicuna, Jose Miguel, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Villar, Eugene Vullimay, Chloe Wakoski, Diane Walker, Mary Ann, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Waller, Rhoda Wanling, Bill Wayman, Tom, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Webb, Jon Weeks, Ramona, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Weil, Jim Seiner, Hannah Whigham, Peter, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Whitney, J.D. Wilentz, Ted and Eli, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Wilson, Keith Wonder, Richard, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Young, Alberto, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "V-Z" Miscellaneous Valerio, Ruben Valle, Gil B. Valle, Jose Luis Vance, Dora Vargas Beal, Ali Vaughan, James Felde, Paul Venegas, Pascual Vezzani, Lee Anne Vilaro, Rodolfo Villanueva, Tino Weatherby, Tom Welburn, Ron Wheeler, Edward Williams, Miller Woolf, Douglas Wright, Jay Zack, David Zimmerman, Toni Zumaran Paz, Jorge, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - A-D Unidentified, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - E-H Unidentified, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - J-N Unidentified, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - O-Z Unidentified, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Margaret Randall to Sergion Mondragon, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Arango, Gonzalo, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ariceaga, Alejandro Bertoni, Claudio, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Canzani, D. Ariel Fodoresky, Raquel and Dayal, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Fortique, Cesar Garzun Cespedes, Francisco, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Gottleib, Saul Hurtado,Rogelio Fabio, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Scott Lammers, Han, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "A-G" Little Magazines, Reviews etc, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Lalo, Edwardo, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Preler, Horacio Reymena, Ricardo Ross, Ciro Bianchi, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Schleifer, Abdullah Suarez, Adolfo Tipping, Richard, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Toti, Gianni Valverde, Umberto, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Vicunan, Cecilia [pseud.] Zola, Edward, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Series C: Printed Materials
  This series contains an incomplete collection of printed materials divided into three subseries. Subseries 1 includes annotated typescripts for issues 24-31. Subseries 2 contains page proofs for issues 24-30. Subseries 3 contains galley proofs for issues 24, 35, 27-31.
  - Subseries 1: Annotated Typescripts
    - Issue 24, October 1967 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Issue 29, January 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Issue 31, May/June 1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Issue 25, January 1968, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Issue 26, April 1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Issue 27, July 1968 [missing some pages] (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Issue 28, October 1968 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Issue 30, April 1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2: Page Proofs
    - Issue #24, pages 1-100. October 1967., u1967 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Issue #24, pages 101-175. October 1967 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Issue #25, pages 2-144. January 1968. [copied, not original page proofs] (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Issue #25, 81-150. January 1968 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Issue #26, pages 1-114. April 1968 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Issue #27, pages 1-173. July 1968. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Issue #28, pages 1-152. October 1968. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Issue #29, pages 1-136. January 1969. (Box 12, Folder 1)